

# Fahad Ashraf Chaudhry

**BS** Information Technology



sh.fahadashraf@gmail.com







I'm a full stack geek with a lot of love for latest technologies. Experienced in **Ionic** Framework, ASP.NET, JAVA/Android and UI/UX Designing. I'm an excellent communicator and focus on using my interpersonal skills to build state-of-the-art softwares and user interfaces!

# Experiences

December 2015 - Current

## Web Developer

Aik Pencil UX, Lahore, Pakistan

2016 - 2017

# Lead Developer

PUCIT ACM Student Chapter, Lahore, Pakistan

2015 - 2016

## **Graphic Designer**

PUCIT ACM Student Chapter, Lahore, Pakistan

July 2015 - October 2015

## **UI/UX** Designer

Trequant, Incubated in Plan9, Lahore, Pakistan

September 2013 - March 2015

#### Web Development Intern

Geniusity, Lahore, Pakistan

April 2014 - February 2015

## Content Generation and Designing

Humans of PUCIT, Lahore, Pakistan

## Education

September 2013 - Current

BS Information Technology – CGPA 3.55 / 4.0 Punjab University College of Information Technology Lahore, Pakistan

2011 - 2013

FSc. Pre Engineering

Pak Fazaia College

Lahore, Pakistan

# **Projects**

# Snazzout (Final Year Project)

A hybrid application, made on **Ionic Framework** that allows users to search different brands, rate/review them and stay updated to their latest news.

#### Aik Pencil UX

AIK PENCIL UX is a UI/UX Agency that deals with designing and development of web and mobile interfaces.

#### **PASC** Website

PUCIT ACM Student Chapter Website for thier Events/ Contact/Updates and Team information, built on Wordpress.

## UI/UX/Designing Projects

Some of my UI/UX Design work on behance, follow this link: https://www.behance.net/fahadachaudhry

A very standard news publication website, developed on ASP.NET that allows the users to select from predefined categories and get news related to those categories.

# ME-ME Generator

An on going project that is intended to provide a very simple platform for students to publish their Resume online. Front-end handled in **AngularJS** while background made in ASP.NET WebAPI.

### **Awards**

- 1. Selected in Principal's list of Spring 2015 GPA 4:00
- 2. Selected in Principal's list of Fall 2015 GPA 3.68
- 3. Selected in Principal's list of Fall 2016 3.76

## Tools

Visual Studio **NetBeans** Atom Sketch 3.0 Photoshop Illustrator Jira Agile Slack Trello

# Design Skills

Mobile design Web design Print design Illustration Photography

# **Development Skills**

Ionic Framework, Android, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Javascript, AngularJS, C/C++/C#, Java, .NET MVC, Structured Query Language (SQL), Wordpress

# Hobies





